

January 19, 2023

Dear CEREO Contact Team,

We are thrilled at the opportunity to connect with you and explore the potential for collaboration on your innovative project, the "Living Atlas". We believe that our expertise and skills can contribute to the success of the Living Atlas project and we are excited to discuss the potential of this collaboration further with you. We look forward to discussing the details of the Living Atlas platform with you and how we can work together to make it a reality.

Sincerely,

The Living Atlas Development Team

W

Joshua Long

github.com/joshmainac (509) 778-8389 – joshua.long@wsu.edu

Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Washington State University, Pullman, WA

Expected Graduation: Fall 2023

Work Experience

GoEco -- Volunteer Teaching Abroad

June 2017 - Sep 2017

- GoEco is a leading organization that provides volunteer opportunities for individuals to teach abroad in underprivileged communities
- As a teacher in GoEco, I was responsible for planning and delivering engaging and effective lessons to students of all ages and abilities, in underprivileged communities

Projects

Excel Spreadsheet

Sep 2022 - Dec 2022

- Developed a spreadsheet application with various features and functionality, using C# and .NET
- Add features such as referencing other cells in formulas, an undo and redo system, and the ability to choose the background color of a cell

Shopping Cart App for Ecommerce

Aug 2022 - Sep 2022

- Developed an application for e-commerce that will add and delete items
- Using react for my primary front-end framework
- Designed RESTful back-end server using MySQL and node.

Personal Portfolio Website + external API

July 2022 - Aug 2022

- Created a personal website using HTML, CSS, javascript, react
- Joker API to fetch a random joke when a user opens the website

Technical Skills

- C/C++
- C#

- Python
- HTML/CSS
- JavaScript/React
- Node.js
- MongoDB
- MYSQL

Mitchell Kolb

github.com/Mitchell-kolb (509) 844-8922 – mitchell.kolb@wsu.edu

Education

High School Diploma Graduated: Spring 2019

Gonzaga Preparatory School, Spokane, WA

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science Expected Graduation: Fall 2023

Washington State University, Pullman, WA

Work Experience

Safeway Grocery Store -- Bakery Production

June 2021 - Current

• Work with a team of bakers to prepare a variety of breads and pastries

Albertsons Grocery Store -- Front-End / Meat Dept. Clerk

Feb 2018 - Aug 2019

 Worked mainly as a Courtesy Clerk which included bagging groceries and providing excellent customer service

Projects

Class Scheduler Website

Aug 2020 - Jan 2021

- Produced a Full Stack application by a team of 4 people where users can apply for courses and communicate with professors in that course.
- Used HTML/CSS for the front end and Flask/SQLAchemy for backend and database
- Project was completed using the Agile software method

Galaga Game Built with Partner using SFML/C++

Feb 2020 - May 2020

- Arcade like game using sprites and collision detection in the SFML library
- Used C++ Inheritance and Polymorphism

Technical Skills

C/C++

Python + Pandas

Github

• Linux/Ubuntu

• HTML/CSS

Flask + SQLAchemy

Sierra Svetlik

github.com/SierraSv

(206) 334-3744 – sierra.svetlik@wsu.edu

Education

High School Diploma Graduated: Spring 2019

Highline High School, Burien, WA

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science Expected Graduation: Fall 2023

Washington State University, Pullman, WA

Work Experience

The Bookie -- Cashier October 2021 - Current

- Provide service to customers and help them purchase their choice of products
- Help with any other tasks asked of me

Projects

Hangman Game built solo using Python

October 2021 - July 2022

- Text only (no graphics) hangman game
- Includes word list creation, editing, and deletion capabilities

Business Review App with Partners using C#/SQL

Feb. 2022 – April 2022

- Built from scratch application using a database from Yelp
- Used C# for the app and SQL to parse the data per user request

Piano Keys Game Built with Partner using SFML/C++

Winter 2020

- Based off of similar piano tiles/keys games that can be found in app stores
- Designed as a PC game
- Made use of hash tables for data storage

Bricks Breaker Game Built with Partner using SFML/C++ $\,$

Spring 2020

- Arcade like game using sprites and collision detection in the SFML library
- Used C++ Inheritance

Technical Skills

• C/C++

Python

Github

- Linux/Ubuntu
- SQL